[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "You're not implacably opposed to running for president?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "implacably", "opposed", "to", "running", "for", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "No, I'm not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "Could America be ready for another Bush in the White House?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "America", "be", "ready", "for", "another", "Bush", "in", "the", "White", "House", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "I mean, look, this is a time to serve.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "look", ",", "this", "is", "a", "time", "to", "serve", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "PERSON": ["Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["San Francisco"], "TIME": ["this morning"]}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "And what did you think of last night?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "did", "you", "think", "of", "last", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Well, I didn't see it because I was flying out to San Francisco, but this morning, bright and early, I saw what other people thought of the debate.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "see", "it", "because", "I", "was", "flying", "out", "to", "San", "Francisco", ",", "but", "this", "morning", ",", "bright", "and", "early", ",", "I", "saw", "what", "other", "people", "thought", "of", "the", "debate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "I mean he's -- he's consistent, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "he", "'s", "--", "he", "'s", "consistent", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "He's very consistent.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "very", "consistent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Are you prepared to do this?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "prepared", "to", "do", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, I don't have as much weight behind me as Chris Christie, but I'm getting up there.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "as", "much", "weight", "behind", "me", "as", "Chris", "Christie", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "getting", "up", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "What should America be doing -- what should American politicians be doing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "America", "be", "doing", "--", "what", "should", "American", "politicians", "be", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "VBG", ":", "WP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "I think I have a sense of history, for starters.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "have", "a", "sense", "of", "history", ",", "for", "starters", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "You support their right to protest?", "question_tokens": ["You", "support", "their", "right", "to", "protest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Oh, yes, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "So we should blame your brother, basically?", "question_tokens": ["So", "we", "should", "blame", "your", "brother", ",", "basically", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Well, we do that all the time, but not in this particular case.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "do", "that", "all", "the", "time", ",", "but", "not", "in", "this", "particular", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["September of 2008"]}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Do you feel confident that enough is being done to prevent that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "confident", "that", "enough", "is", "being", "done", "to", "prevent", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "You know, I think -- I think our banks are stronger today than they were in September of 2008, and they're certainly stronger in terms of their capital ratios compared to the European banks.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "our", "banks", "are", "stronger", "today", "than", "they", "were", "in", "September", "of", "2008", ",", "and", "they", "'re", "certainly", "stronger", "in", "terms", "of", "their", "capital", "ratios", "compared", "to", "the", "European", "banks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Asia"]}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Do you think it's kind of anti the culture of the country?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "kind", "of", "anti", "the", "culture", "of", "the", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "It feels -- when you travel to Asia, particularly, you know, you get this spirit of optimism that's quite remarkable, and also a feeling that they look at us and kind of say, you know, poor older brother, you know, your days are behind you.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "feels", "--", "when", "you", "travel", "to", "Asia", ",", "particularly", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "get", "this", "spirit", "of", "optimism", "that", "'s", "quite", "remarkable", ",", "and", "also", "a", "feeling", "that", "they", "look", "at", "us", "and", "kind", "of", "say", ",", "you", "know", ",", "poor", "older", "brother", ",", "you", "know", ",", "your", "days", "are", "behind", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Why has education always been your great passion?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "has", "education", "always", "been", "your", "great", "passion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Well, I think I learned it at my mama's knee to start with.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "I", "learned", "it", "at", "my", "mama", "'s", "knee", "to", "start", "with", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "Quite frightening, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Quite", "frightening", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "It's very frightening.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "very", "frightening", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "Why has nobody really got to grits with this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "has", "nobody", "really", "got", "to", "grits", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Look, I think -- I think our country has rested on its laurels.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "our", "country", "has", "rested", "on", "its", "laurels", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["10 percent"]}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "And how much should be driven from the state?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "much", "should", "be", "driven", "from", "the", "state", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Well, today, it's anywhere from 8 to 10 percent.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "today", ",", "it", "'s", "anywhere", "from", "8", "to", "10", "percent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "What do you think is the optimum?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "is", "the", "optimum", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Where it is today is fine in terms of the relevance of education.", "answer_tokens": ["Where", "it", "is", "today", "is", "fine", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "relevance", "of", "education", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "What are the key, simple ways that other states, and therefore America, collectively, can get to grips with this corrosive education system?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "key", ",", "simple", "ways", "that", "other", "states", ",", "and", "therefore", "America", ",", "collectively", ",", "can", "get", "to", "grips", "with", "this", "corrosive", "education", "system", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "MD", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "A focus on early childhood literacy, so the children come prepared to learn.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "focus", "on", "early", "childhood", "literacy", ",", "so", "the", "children", "come", "prepared", "to", "learn", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["21st century"]}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Do even teachers' unions get this, do you think, or is this still, again, a very old-fashioned sense of what a union should be doing?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "even", "teachers", "'", "unions", "get", "this", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "or", "is", "this", "still", ",", "again", ",", "a", "very", "old-fashioned", "sense", "of", "what", "a", "union", "should", "be", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "This is like one of those fights in the previous segment, I believe, that we're -- that it's the transition from kind of the old '70s way of doing things to the 21st century way of doing things.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "like", "one", "of", "those", "fights", "in", "the", "previous", "segment", ",", "I", "believe", ",", "that", "we", "'re", "--", "that", "it", "'s", "the", "transition", "from", "kind", "of", "the", "old", "'70s", "way", "of", "doing", "things", "to", "the", "21st", "century", "way", "of", "doing", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "What's the trick to being successful in Florida, if you're a Republican candidate right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "trick", "to", "being", "successful", "in", "Florida", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "a", "Republican", "candidate", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Well, Florida's an incredible -- it's purple, it's very purple.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Florida", "'s", "an", "incredible", "--", "it", "'s", "purple", ",", "it", "'s", "very", "purple", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "What's it like having a brother and a dad who have both been president of the United States?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "it", "like", "having", "a", "brother", "and", "a", "dad", "who", "have", "both", "been", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "It's different.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "different", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Do you have to have that ability to cope with huge pressure, but also have the family, the balance?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "to", "have", "that", "ability", "to", "cope", "with", "huge", "pressure", ",", "but", "also", "have", "the", "family", ",", "the", "balance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Well, that's an extraordinary thing to witness, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "an", "extraordinary", "thing", "to", "witness", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "And we didn't talk about it.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "we", "did", "n't", "talk", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "What was the toughest things for you to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "toughest", "things", "for", "you", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "I would say in the second term, the turning against him because of the war was difficult.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "in", "the", "second", "term", ",", "the", "turning", "against", "him", "because", "of", "the", "war", "was", "difficult", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Was that the right thing to do?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "the", "right", "thing", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Does he miss being president?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "miss", "being", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "I'm sure he misses the White House, misses the service.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sure", "he", "misses", "the", "White", "House", ",", "misses", "the", "service", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Why not personally?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "personally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Well, because it's personal.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", "it", "'s", "personal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":"], "qSentId": 403, "question": "ORGAN: Can you see yourself running in the future?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Can", "you", "see", "yourself", "running", "in", "the", "future", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "I can --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "Isn't it like a calling for you Bushes now?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "like", "a", "calling", "for", "you", "Bushes", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "NNPS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "No, it isn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "is", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", ":", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Could you see the situation where the personal reasons, which I won't press you on -- but where those would go away enough for you to consider running perhaps in 2016?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "see", "the", "situation", "where", "the", "personal", "reasons", ",", "which", "I", "wo", "n't", "press", "you", "on", "--", "but", "where", "those", "would", "go", "away", "enough", "for", "you", "to", "consider", "running", "perhaps", "in", "2016", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ":", "CC", "WRB", "DT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "That's pure -- that's just hypothetical, so I can't answer.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "pure", "--", "that", "'s", "just", "hypothetical", ",", "so", "I", "ca", "n't", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "You're not implacably opposed to running for president?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "implacably", "opposed", "to", "running", "for", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "No, I'm not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "You don't just imagine one day just walking into the Oval Office?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "just", "imagine", "one", "day", "just", "walking", "into", "the", "Oval", "Office", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "CD", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Let's move to digital learn.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "move", "to", "digital", "learn", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Oval Office"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Is this a scoop?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "a", "scoop", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "This is a scoop.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "a", "scoop", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Some of this, Governor Bush, does modern technology help kids learn better and faster than the old-fashioned technology?", "question_tokens": ["Some", "of", "this", ",", "Governor", "Bush", ",", "does", "modern", "technology", "help", "kids", "learn", "better", "and", "faster", "than", "the", "old-fashioned", "technology", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "I believe that passionately.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "that", "passionately", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 470, "question": "What is your view about competition, whether it's sporting or academic, in schools in America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "about", "competition", ",", "whether", "it", "'s", "sporting", "or", "academic", ",", "in", "schools", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "I think --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Are you in favor of egg and spoon races?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "in", "favor", "of", "egg", "and", "spoon", "races", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "What do you think, Governor Bush?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", ",", "Governor", "Bush", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "I think he's wrong.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "wrong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Governor Wise?", "question_tokens": ["Governor", "Wise", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "I happen to think -- I agree with Warren Buffett on the taxes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "happen", "to", "think", "--", "I", "agree", "with", "Warren", "Buffett", "on", "the", "taxes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Do you know how many people you both executed?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "many", "people", "you", "both", "executed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "DT", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I think during eight years, I've probably -- I'm going to be off a little bit, probably 50 people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "during", "eight", "years", ",", "I", "'ve", "probably", "--", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "be", "off", "a", "little", "bit", ",", "probably", "50", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "If you had the decision, if you were the president of the United States, would you try now and stop the death penalty?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "the", "decision", ",", "if", "you", "were", "the", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", ",", "would", "you", "try", "now", "and", "stop", "the", "death", "penalty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "How are you going to link it to education?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "going", "to", "link", "it", "to", "education", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "ISE: Because DNA is modern technology.", "answer_tokens": ["ISE", ":", "Because", "DNA", "is", "modern", "technology", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Let me ask you first, Governor Bush?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", "first", ",", "Governor", "Bush", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Consistently higher graduation rates.", "answer_tokens": ["Consistently", "higher", "graduation", "rates", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}}]